{
    "subject": "resource/The_Story_of_Sin",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:Polish_films",
    "human_readable": "The subject of 'The Story of Sin' is Polish films.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8536116480827332,
            "question": "Does 'The Story of Sin' offer historical context about Polish cinema?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8453047871589661,
            "question": "Could 'The Story of Sin' include interviews with filmmakers or actors from Poland?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8273351192474365,
            "question": "What could be some common themes in Polish films featured in 'The Story of Sin'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7569652795791626,
            "question": "What is the subject of 'The Story of Sin'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7562861442565918,
            "question": "How might 'The Story of Sin' explore the evolution of Polish filmmaking?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.677006721496582,
            "question": "Are there any other genres besides Polish films explored in 'The Story of Sin'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.638982892036438,
            "question": "What impact might watching 'The Story of Sin' have on viewers' understanding of Polish culture?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5869774222373962,
            "question": "What type of films are featured in 'The Story of Sin'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3750929832458496,
            "question": "Is 'The Story of Sin' about a specific director or actor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1521320343017578,
            "question": "What makes Polish films unique compared to other national cinemas?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The subject of 'The Story of Sin' is Polish films.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4610_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is 'The Story of Sin' about a specific director or actor?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4610_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of films are featured in 'The Story of Sin'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4610_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What impact might watching 'The Story of Sin' have on viewers' understanding of Polish culture?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4610_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4610_107.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4610_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4610_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4610_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4610_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4610_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4610_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4610_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4610_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4610_82.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple \"The subject of 'The Story of Sin' is Polish films.\"\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation:\n\n* The documents mention that \"The Story of Sin\" is a 1975 Polish drama film directed by Walerian Borowczyk.\n* The text also talks about the film's place in the context of Polish cinema and its contribution to the global cinema landscape.\n* Additionally, the title of the document \"THE STORY OF SIN (Dzieje grzechu) (1975) - \u2666\u2666\u2666\" explicitly mentions that it is a Polish period drama.\n\nOverall, the information in the documents supports the triple."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The provided context information discusses the film \"The Story of Sin,\" which is indeed a Polish drama film directed by Walerian Borowczyk. Therefore, the statement that the subject of 'The Story of Sin' is Polish films is supported by the documents."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "'The subject of 'The Story of Sin' is Polish films.' is incorrect as 'The Story of Sin' is a specific film produced in Poland, not the entirety of Polish cinema.",
            "category": 3
        }
    }
}